This is so good!
Real good?
The worst thing about the dungeon is not being able to eat this good when we're in it.
Let's savor it while we can.
Hey there, Kabru!
Haven't seen you around.
I heard you've been doing amazing lately.
Well, I don't know about amazing.
Seems like yesterday you all were just a bunch of rookies.
But look at you now.
It's great you guys are still together.
Big parties are rare these days.
Why do you think that is?
They go missing or just get sick of each other.
Fighting over money is a big reason.
But your party's been together for a while, so maybe you'll be the ones to kill the Mad Mage.
Yeah, right.
We're not that good yet.
Don't sell yourself short.
Why are you like that?
Huh?
Instead of playing coy with that idiot, you should have just come right out and said it.
Of course we'll be the ones to take out the Mad Mage.
We could never settle for being bottom-rung adventurers such as that, Goon.
Wren, Wren, they'll know us all by our actions instead of our words.
Here's the plan.
Today we'll go deeper into the dungeon.
Let's gear up and get ready.
Welcome.
Hello there.
One week's food and two days' water for six people, please.
Here you go.
Dealing with food is a bigger pain than the monsters the deeper down we go.
A week's worth of food is heavy.
Some people stay in for a month.
How do they do it?
Well, McBell...
What they do is...
They kill the parties they meet and feast on their flesh!
It'd be way easier to hunt monsters for food than other parties.
You are what folks call a wet blanket.
For our first time going down this deep, we're doing amazing.
At this rate, we're going to get farther than anyone.
Well, we're doing great so far, but stay sharp.
Who knows what's waiting up ahead?
I heard things have been strange here lately.
Some say the monsters are getting more aggressive.
Others say the layout here has been changing.
It definitely feels a lot weirder than before.
Better to be safe than sorry.
Kaurburu!
Look at this!
I got it off this zombie!
Let's open it.
Don't waste your time with that thing.
What's the harm in checking?
There could be gold in it.
We've never found anything good in those before.
There must be a good reason why this zombie had a death grip on it, literally speaking.
It would be dumb to not take a peek.
Huh?
No way!
Gold and jewels!
We hit the jackpot!
We're rich!
I can't believe it!
Hot diggity.
What a hole.
I thought by now the dungeon would be picked clean of all the treasure.
Oh well.
Like they say, things happen strange here.
We so needed a brick like this.
Now we can afford the supplies we need to go deeper.
Guys, how about we all head back to town for some dinner?
Does that sound good?
Yeah!
Huh?
Whoa.
These guys got wiped out big time.
Oh no.
Looks like they were headed back to town too.
How awful.
I don't see any wounds on them.
Maybe a ghost killed them.
Or they starved to death.
And it looks to me like they killed each other over this treasure.
I, um, I'm sure the corpse retrievers will find them soon.
But I'll cast a spell so they don't turn into zombies.
This was Fallon's specialty though.
What do you want to do about all this treasure?
Let's pile it up and leave it for them.
I bet most of it's gonna end up in the pockets of the corpse retrievers.
What?
Are you okay back there?
Yeah.
Sure am.
Why'd my sword twitch?
Hey, let go of my hand.
You're gonna give yourself away.
What do you want?
Hurry.
Draw me.
I can feel it telling me there's danger.
Marcel!
Ah!
Get away from there!
Huh?
A stun spell.
I'm glad it wasn't an explosion spell.
What the heck? Treasure insects?
Oh, gross!
Bees killed them? Never seen one up close like this before.
I can't tell the difference from real treasure.
But a minute ago you could tell.
Yeah, he's right. You even drew your sword.
Oh, um, I thought I saw one of them move?
Liar.
The critter and my sword sensed them.
It's calm now, so that's gotta be it.
Is it just me or is it getting weirder?
Huh?
Hmm.
Yum.
You have got to be kidding me.
These you can eat. These you can't.
Do they taste any good?
Oh, I'll say they do.
Bugs got all the nutrients a body needs.
Cook these suckers up right and you got yourself a meal.
Hell, they're a feast for the eyes, too.
Not if you're seeing it from this angle.
How can you tell which are or aren't edible?
Hmm, it depends.
For example, this one's easy.
If you look between the beads, you can see its teeny legs.
With brooches and coins, you check the backside.
I think it's neat how the male and female coin bugs have different faces.
With rings, if they're flexible, they're a bug.
Tiaras need to be put in water to tell for sure.
Bugs are light, so if it floats, you got yourself bugs.
Let's cook these suckers before the stun spell wears off.
For the necklace, pull off all the legs.
The texture ain't great if you leave them on.
Then skewer and roast it.
Heat up some oil and give the coin bugs a good frown, stomach side down.
Drop in a pinch of salt and stir them so the oil gets around evenly.
There.
Flip them spine side up so they look pretty.
Pour the tiara, pop out the eggs and larva from their nest.
Risk it up in the pot and boil everything together.
Spoon it into a jar and...
It's ready.
Looks nice, but they still don't look much like food to me.
Then again, it's not my first time eating these things.
I heard they're some kind of regional cuisine.
Some say eating them brings luck.
I'll find out in a sec.
Those taste way better than the ones I had.
Of course it does.
The monsters you get from the dungeon always got better flavor than the ones on the surface.
Folks up top can try raising them, but they just don't taste the same.
Uh...
Dear lord, it's creamy.
I'm never gonna wear neckses again.
This kinda tastes like fish.
Ow!
If we find some deeper down, they'll taste even better.
I can't wait.
Oh!
Thank you.
Ow!
Mm.
Wow.
That's sweet.
Can't get over how real they look.
They use mimicry to hide from their enemies.
Just like you, sword critter.
Is that why you reacted to them?
Hmm.
Mm.
Can I try one?
Hm.
Hmm.
Huh?
It's nothing.
Oh.
It thought it was a threat.
It was trying to warn me.
I think it thinks we're a team now.
How cute.
I have to give you a name.
Ready to get going?
What are we supposed to do with the ones you said we can't eat?
Toss them, if you want.
If someone were to eat one of these, what would you do?
What would you do?
What would you do with the ones you said we can't eat?
Toss them, if you want.
If someone were to eat one of these, what would you do?
What would you do with them?
Are they poisonous or do they just taste bad?
What are you talking about?
You'd break your teeth.
You can't eat real treasure.
You could break your teeth.
What would you do with me?
What would you do with them now?
How cute.
I have to give you a name?
Ready to get going?
What are we supposed to do with the ones you said we can't eat?
Toss them, if you want.
If someone were to eat one of these, what would happen to them?
Don't you tell them, not to their own house?
You need to drink.
What are you talking about?
You break your teeth.
You can't eat real treasure.
Real treasure. Real treasure.
Treasure. Treasure.
Why didn't you say that before?
Got it.
From now on, your name's Kensuke.
You're eating another one of those things?
We got a lot of leftovers.
Honestly, this isn't a picnic.
Great. The temperature dropped.
All those shimmery blobs.
Yeah, those are ghosts gathering.
Go, before they see us.
Ghosts?
They're drawn to the corpses we just left behind.
Hmm. We should just blast them with a spell and...
That's right.
Fallon's not here.
I miss her, too.
I cast a protection spell on that party.
I had to rush it a bit, but the ghosts won't possess...
Ghost. Behind us. Run!
Oh, that idiot!
My ears.
Hurry, get up. More are coming.
They're all riled up from that explosion.
Don't you know any less flashy magic spells?
You know, something simple?
Like the kind Fallon always used.
Are you kidding me?
She used high-level magic.
There was nothing simple about it.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
It's true.
She's an awesome magic user.
Dealing with ghosts was no sweat for her.
Lifgant.
Odenbaum.
There!
That's all there is to it.
Those pesky ghosts can't harm you now.
If any show up, an explosion spell could take them all out quick.
You could do that easy, Fallon.
If possible, I'd prefer to avoid doing that.
It doesn't get rid of them.
After they're blown to bits, they just reform again anyway.
And I don't want to make them suffer.
You're so kind.
That's nice you're giving them the benefit of the doubt.
But if ghosts go around possessing people's bodies...
I think they deserve to get their butts kicked.
Mm-hmm.
That guy's on the missing adventurer list, all right.
Okay, I'll take care of them.
First, I'll knock them...
I'll do it.
This can be handled without violence.
No!
Fallon, wait!
Be at peace.
And leave this body.
Fallon!
She sounds like a heck of a person.
Yeah.
Fallon was amazing.
I mean, is.
But...
If the ghosts catch up to us...
I'll have to use my magic to stop them.
Oh, no, you won't.
There's no way you can blow up every single one of them.
I'll do it just like Fallon did.
I'll give them all a gentle embrace.
A gentle embrace of explosions.
No.
Gentle explosions.
No!
You said yourself you can't do it like Fallon, so just leave them alone!
She'd trust me to do the right thing!
Okay, then what will you do if you run out of mana?
I won't.
I can use my weaker explosion spells to blow them up.
There are no weak explosion spells!
Guys, enough.
Hate to say it, folks, but it don't look like we're gonna outrun these creepies.
The longer we stand around arguing, the faster they'll catch up to us.
Wait, what are you doing?
Gonna whip up a little something to keep the ghosts off us.
What kind of thing?
A holy water thing.
Wait, you have holy water?
Nope.
Gotta make some.
You can make that?
Didn't know you were a cleric, too.
There's all kinds of custom in the world to get rid of evil stuff.
Fire's one of them.
It keeps the dark back, and it can create and destroy.
All through history, folks have used it as a sacred symbol and a holy ward to keep that evil the hell away from you.
Yeah, I know all that, but candles aren't gonna keep ghosts back.
One candle might not help much, but a bunch of them all lit up and flickering away?
That's a lot of holy power.
The golden rhinoceros beetle's another secret thing.
To some folks, they were symbols of the sun and the sun god.
A lot of love for those critters.
Ooze is holy, too.
It's used as an offering to the gods and to purify whatever it is it needs purifying.
Then there's salt.
Tradition's going way back, saying it protects against evil and purifies the body.
And since sugar looks the same, I'll add some of that.
Not sure how potent it'll be, so I'll dump a bunch in to be safe.
You're making this up as you go!
Not a bad idea to add some herbs.
And what the heck, dried monster guts, too.
Then we'll add the power of fire to the mix.
The holy water's ready.
Here they come!
Just gotta make sure the lid's tight on the holy water.
What are you doing? Aren't you gonna use it?
I will, as soon as I tie this rope to the jar.
We're gonna die here.
Oh, no.
Thelen.
I'm alive.
Because of you.
If only the dragon ate me instead,
our friends wouldn't be in this mess.
Forgive me.
Holy crap!
I saw my dad on the other side!
It's working.
Every ghost he hits gets driven away.
Only water works.
Even in a jar.
It works amazingly.
Maybe I've been possessed this whole time by Fallon.
How could you say that?
Fallon would never.
And she hasn't even turned into a ghost yet.
No, that's not what I mean.
I couldn't get over the fact that we don't have her help.
And thinking about how easy things would be if we did.
But the reality is, she's not here.
Until she's back, we gotta help ourselves.
Yeah, you're right.
Senchi!
Let me take a crack at him.
It's over.
The jar's got frost on it.
Using holy water like that's more efficient than spraying it all over.
That figures.
Ghost can pass through the jar so the water hits him.
Hmm?
Well, I'll be.
It's sorbet.
Is it safe to eat something with ghost funk all over it?
I'm more worried about what holy water this powerful is gonna do to our stomachs.
I'm worried about how much sugar I've had today.
It's great!
He's right!
It's good!
It's so light and refreshing, too!
Instead of getting cursed by ghosts, we got blessed.
You said it!
You said there's monster in this.
What did you end up using?
Just some grated slime guts.
Oh, that explains the jiggly texture.
But it's still so smooth and creamy.
Hey, guys.
Get this.
We're so lucky.
If Fallon didn't get eaten, we wouldn't be having sorbet now.
Huh?
You're joking, right?
It sounds like you're happy that she got eaten.
You're, like, the worst brother ever!
But I was just saying...
You know, some things are better to keep to yourself.
Oh, jeez.
If only Fallon were here.
There's a positive side to every bad situation.
She'd say something like that and pack me up.
I don't know if it's me or this sorbet,
but the vibe here got chillier.
Come back, Fallon.
We need you!